Oh, uh, yeah. I got them on Amazon.
(Stuart:)Sure. I get it.
(Stuart:)Why support a friend when you can support
a multinational conglomerate...
(Stuart:)...that is crushing the life
out of that friend?
(Leonard:)I know, but when I shop online
I can do it on the toilet.
(Stuart:)Have you seen my store?
The whole place is a toilet.
- Can we please move this along?
- Yeah, sorry.
(Leonard:)Uh, you come to the end of the tunnel
and find a large chest.
(Leonard:)What do you do? And Howard, do not say,
"I feel up the large chest."
(Howard:)Excuse me, I'm a married man now.
I wasn't going to say anything so juvenile.
- Great, what do you do?
- I walk up to the large chest...
...bury my face in it and go:
(Sheldon:)I open the chest.
(Leonard:)It's locked, but suddenly the door
behind you slams shut...
(Leonard:)...and now the walls of the room
start closing in.
(Stuart:)That's not good. My character and I
both have claustrophobia.
(Leonard:)Glowing letters appear on the chest
that read: